mytoshiba.com.au 2019-07-05

# Privacy Statement :: Dynabook :: Laptops/Notebooks, Storage & Accessories

Dynabook ANZ Pty Limited and its related Dynabook group companies (‘Dynabook’) are committed to protecting your privacy.

Dynabook is bound by, and is committed to complying with the Australian Privacy Principles as provided within the Privacy Act 1988 (Commonwealth) (“the ‘Act”) and any other relevant laws, regulations, and/or codes that relate to your Personal Information. This policy outlines precisely how Dynabook treats Personal Information that it collects and/or receives. The definition of “personal information” is quite broad, and refers to information that is about you, in any form, and that could reasonably identify you. Examples of such information include, but are not limited to your name, contact details, address, email address(es), social media information, credit history information, payment card details, and bank account details. 

Dynabook considers the management of Personal Information to be of paramount consideration, and commits to treating Personal Information with the care and consideration it would expect that others would with respect to its own Personal Information. Options available to Dynabook with regard to management include, but are not limited to use of password-protected technology, use of encryption technology, as well as use of Confidentiality Agreements. At all times, Dynabook shall implement both external and internal practices and policies to ensure management of Personal Information occurs in an open and transparent manner. 

Dynabook may collect Personal Information from you, in the event you consent to the collection of Personal Information, and that collection of Personal Information is relevant to Dynabook’s functions or activities. Examples include, but are not limited to Dynabook collecting your Personal Information when you visit or use Dynabook web pages, use Dynabook related software, use Dynabook apps, request or send information through this website, purchase through this website, apply for a credit account with Dynabook, and/or when you send feedback to, or otherwise deal with Dynabook. Dynabook will only collect and hold your Personal Information if it is reasonably necessary for Dynabook’s functions and/or the service we can provide to you. When you request information through this site, we need to know the location that information is to be sent to, and we will use this location to send to you the information you request in the form that you require. We will not pass your details to anyone else outside Dynabook or to approved business partners without your permission.

When you send feedback we ask for relevant contact details to thank you for your contribution and if required, to request more information. If you provide feedback to us, you agree that information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Dynabook may use such information on an unrestricted basis.

When you apply for a credit account with Dynabook, we ask for Personal Information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, bank details, and any other Personal Information we believe may be relevant to the application. By completing and submitting a credit application to Dynabook, you are not acting in an anonymous manner.

When you purchase products online from Dynabook, we ask for Personal Information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address and payment details (e.g credit card details), as well as other Personal Information we believe may be relevant to the purchase. By purchasing products online from Dynabook, you are not acting in an anonymous manner.

Dynabook may also automatically receive and record information from the use of our site or apps. Such information may include your server address, top level domain name (eg. .com, .gov, .au etc), the date and time of the visit, the pages accessed, documents downloaded, the previous site visited, as well as general information about browsing habits and behaviour. By gathering information about your preferences and attributes, we can tailor our service offerings to your needs, and ultimately, provide you with goods and services in accordance with your requirements. 

Dynabook may also collect your personal information from third parties such as credit providers and credit reporting bodies. Contact information and credit information may be collected from third parties when assessing any application for a credit account, guarantee, or the supply of goods and services.

Dynabook generally uses your personal information for purposes including, but not being limited to: i) assessing any applications for credit, processing, and completing any purchase orders, administering your account, fulfiling your request for information or correcting your personal information, contacting you, improving and developing our products and services, and, from time to time, providing information to you regarding products and services that we believe may be of interest to you, as well as other related purposes. Some of the main consequences of not collecting your personal information are that any applications for credit or supply of goods and services may not be processed, we may not be able to respond to your questions, and we may not be able to process orders made to Dynabook.

Dynabook may disclose your personal information to organisations such as:

  * Credit providers, credit reporting bodies and guarantors to assist in assessing any applications for credit;
  * Third party suppliers involved in administering any credit account with Dynabook, and to whom personal information is usually disclosed, with these suppliers including debt collectors, legal advisors, and trade insurers;
  * Third party suppliers involved in processing and delivering any order placed with Dynabook such as transporters, warehouses, financial institutions, merchants and payment organisations;
  * Third party suppliers involved in reviewing, maintaining and upgrading Dynabook’s business systems.

Your personal information may also be used in connection with purposes associated with such organisations.

Dynabook may also disclose information to other organisations where:

  * You have provided your consent;
  * Dynabook is required to respond to a subpoena or subsequent to legal compulsion;
  * Dynabook believes it is necessary to assist in lessening or preventing a serious threat to life, health or safety of any individual, or to public health; and
  * Dynabook believes it is reasonably necessary in taking action in relation to suspected unlawful activity, serious misconduct, locating a missing person, or as is required or authorised under Australian law or a court/tribunal order

Dynabook may also disclose your personal information to overseas recipients. It is not reasonably practical to list all the countries in which the recipients of your information are likely to be located, but it is likely such countries will include Dynabook related companies in Japan and Singapore, and you consent to this disclosure by providing personal information to Dynabook. In providing this consent, you understand that the overseas recipient may not be accountable under the Act and you may not seek redress under the Act. Whilst the overseas recipient may not be subject to similar obligations as the Australian Privacy Principles, Dynabook will make reasonable efforts to ensure the overseas recipients uphold the principles of the Australia Privacy Principles.

If you do not consent to your information being disclosed to overseas recipients kindly contact Dynabook's privacy officer whose details are outlined below under ‘Contact details for Dynabook’s Privacy Officer’.

Dynabook stores your personal information in several different ways, which may include storage in electronic form or in paper form. The security of your personal information is important to Dynabook, and we take reasonable steps to protect it from misuse, interference, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. Some of the ways we do this include, but are not limited to implementing security access procedures to databases, confidentiality agreements for our employees, and by only allowing access to personal information to individuals once Dynabook is satisfied identification requirements have been met.

Dynabook may use or disclose your personal information to let you know about our products and services or promotions that might be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive any further marketing material from us, please either utilise any relevant Unsubscribe function, or kindly contact Dynabook’s Privacy Officer, whose details are outlined below under ‘Contact details for Dynabook’s Privacy Officer’

You have a right to request access to personal information held by Dynabook, subject to several exceptions authorised by law. If you would like to access your personal information held by Dynabook kindly contact Dynabook’s Privacy Officer, whose details are outlined below under ‘Contact details for Dynabook’s Privacy Officer’. 

You have a right to request to correct your Personal Information, as held by Dynabook. If you believe you need to correct your personal information as held by Dynabook, kindly contact Dynabook’s Privacy Officer, whose details are outlined below under ‘Contact details for Dynabook’s Privacy Officer’. Accordingly, Dynabook will inspect your Personal Information, and advise you as to whether Dynabook believes this Personal Information needs to be corrected. 

You have a right to complain about any breach by Dynabook of the Act, which contains the Australian Privacy Principles, as well as any breach by Dynabook of any relevant authorities, or binding privacy code such as the Credit Reporting Privacy Code.

We would ask that in first instance, you should contact Dynabook’s Privacy Officer, whose details are outlined below under ‘Contact details for Dynabook’s Privacy Officer’. Dynabook should be provided a reasonable time to respond to your complaint.

If you are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint to Dynabook, you may lodge a complaint with the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner whose contact details are below:

Office of the Australian Information Commissioner,   
Level 3, 175 Pitt Street,   
Sydney NSW 2000   
Post: GPO Box 5218 Sydney NSW 2001   
Tel: 1300 363 992   
Email: [enquiries@oaic.gov.au](mailto:enquiries@oaic.gov.au)   
Website: [http://www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/)

The Compliance Manager,   
Corporate Services Division   
Dynabook ANZ Pty Limited  
Postal Address: PO Box 350 North Ryde 1670   
Email address: [privacyofficer@toshiba-tap.com](mailto:privacyofficer@toshiba-tap.com)   
Telephone number: +612 98876000 

Dynabook may update this policy in response to any changes in its business model, and/or any changes to the legal and regulatory landscape governing this policy. 

Other than in respect of personal information, if you provide information to us you agree that information shall be deemed to be non-confidential, and Dynabook may use such information on an unrestricted basis. If you wish to change or delete any of the information you have entered whilst visiting our site or if you have any questions about our privacy statement, kindly contact Dynabook’s privacy officer on +612 9887 6501 or [privacyofficer@toshiba-tap.com](mailto:privacyofficer@toshiba-tap.com) These terms and conditions are governed by the laws in force in the State of New South Wales, Australia. The courts of New South Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute arising out of any Privacy related issues. Unauthorised access of this web site and associated software is unlawful and may result in legal proceedings.
